Guide to the E. L. Wolven Glass Plate Negative Collection, 1897-1944
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series V. Drama, Music and Dance, 1900-1936
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1921, 1922 May 19 (Box 71 [217_16])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1921, 1922 May 19 (Box 71 [217_17])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1921, 1922 May 19 (Box 71 [217_19])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1921, 1922 May 19 (Box 71 [217_20])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1921, 1922 May 19 (Box 71 [217_21])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1921, 1922 May 19 (Box 71 [217_22])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1921, 1922 May 19 (Box 71 [217_23])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1921, 1922 May 19 (Box 71 [217_24])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_01])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_02])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_05])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_12])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_13])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_14])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_15])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_17])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_18])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_19])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_21])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_22])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_23])
  - English speech class play — "Romeo and Juliet,", 1922 May 26 (Box 74 [223_24])
  - French Club play — "Gringoire,", 1922 May 5 (Box 77 [228_01])
  - French Club play — "Gringoire,", 1922 May 5 (Box 77 [228_02])
  - French Club play — "Gringoire,", 1922 May 5 (Box 77 [228_03])
  - French Club play — "Gringoire,", 1922 May 5 (Box 77 [228_08])
  - French Club play — "Gringoire,", 1922 May 5 (Box 77 [228_09])
  - French Club play — "Gringoire,", 1922 May 5 (Box 77 [228_10])
  - French Club play — "Gringoire,", 1922 May 5 (Box 77 [228_11])
  - Sophomore Party — Call-For-A-Package Chorus in the skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Oct 28 (Box 81 [236_19])
  - Sophomore Party — Opening scene of the skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Oct 28 (Box 81/82 [237_09])
  - Sophomore Party — Opening scene, featuring mermaids, lobsters, and an octopus, of the skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Oct 28 (Box 81 [236_18])
  - Sophomore Party — Scene from Act II of the skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1926. Two students are in blackface and costumed as waiters, 1922 Oct 28 (Box 81 [236_20])
  - Sophomore Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Oct 28 (Box 81/82 [237_08])
  - Sophomore Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Oct 28 (Box 81/82 [237_17])
  - Sophomore Party — Three students in a large chicken costume in the skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Oct 28 (Box 95 [Box255_012])
  - Sophomore Party — Wheel Chair Chorus in the skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Oct 28 (Box 81/82 [237_07])
  - Junior Party — Opening scene of the skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144g])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144b])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144c])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144e])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144f])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144h])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144j])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144k])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926. The scene includes eight students in stereotypical Chinese costumes, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144l])
  - Junior Party — Skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926. The scene includes one student costumed as Buddha and three students in stereotypical Chinese or South Asian costumes with symbols relating to money, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144n])
  - Junior Party — Student portraying a Russian dancer in the skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144d])
  - Junior Party — Students portraying representatives of Vassar, West Point and Sing Sing in a skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144i])
  - Junior Party — The "Victrola record chorus" in the skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144])
  - Junior Party — Three students costumed as rag dolls in the skit show presented by the Class of 1924 to the Class of 1926. One doll is a "long-legged" doll and the other two are golliwog dolls and are in blackface, 1922 Nov 11 (Box 59 [package144m])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_04])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_05])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_07])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_09])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_14])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_15])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_19])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_20])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_21])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_22])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 76 [227_08])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 76 [227_17])
  - First Hall Play — "Sabine Women,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 76 [227_18])
  - First Hall Play — "The Birthday of the Infanta,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_06])
  - First Hall Play — "The Birthday of the Infanta,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_08])
  - First Hall Play — "The Birthday of the Infanta,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_10])
  - First Hall Play — "The Birthday of the Infanta,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_11])
  - First Hall Play — "The Birthday of the Infanta,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_12])
  - First Hall Play — "The Birthday of the Infanta,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 75/76 [226_13])
  - First Hall Play — "The Birthday of the Infanta,", 1922 Dec 16 (Box 76 [227_16])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida,", 1923 Mar 10 (Box 57 [package139])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida,", 1923 Mar 10 (Box 57 [package139b])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida,", 1923 Mar 10 (Box 57 [package139c])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida,", 1923 Mar 10 (Box 57 [package139f])
  - Second Hall Play — "Candida,", 1923 Mar 10 (Box 57 [package139g])
  - Founder's Day dance — Morris dancers performing at Founder's Day, 1923 Apr 27 (Box 33 [Box264_017])
  - Founder's Day dance — Morris dancers performing at Founder's Day, 1923 Apr 27 (Box 18 [package101h])
  - Founder's Day dance — Morris dancers performing at Founder's Day, 1923 Apr 27 (Box 18 [package101l])
  - Founder's Day dance — Morris dancers performing at Founder's Day, 1923 Apr 27 (Box 20 [package107])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 67 [210_12])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_001])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_002])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_003])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_004])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_005])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_006])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_007])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_008])
  - Founder's Day play — "Beggar's Opera,", 1923 Apr 27 (Box 55 [Package74_009])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162b])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162c])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162d])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162e])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162f])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162g])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162h])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package162i])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163b])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163c])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163d])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163e])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163f])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163g])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163h])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163i])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1925, 1923 May 18 (Box 60 [package163j])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package44_001])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package44_002])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package44_003])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package44_004])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package44_005])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package44_006])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package45_004])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package45_005])
  - French Club play — "Les Romanesques,", 1923 May 19 (Box 47 [Package45_006])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 73 [221_06])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 88/89 [Box246_019])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 88/89 [Box246_020])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 89 [Box247_002])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 89 [Box247_009])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 89 [Box247_010])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 89 [Box247_013])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 89 [Box247_014])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 57 [package139d])
  - Third Hall Play — "Twelfth Night,", 1923 May 25 (Box 53 [Package66_005])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_05])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_06])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_07])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_08])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_09])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_10])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_11])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_12])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_17])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Life of Henry the Eighth,", 1923 Jun 9 (Box 63 [203_20])
  - Sophomore Party — 1861 minuet dance couple in the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_13])
  - Sophomore Party — 1861 minuet dance couple in the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_14])
  - Sophomore Party — 1861 minuet dance couple in the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_20])
  - Sophomore Party — 1861 minuet dance couple in the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_21])
  - Sophomore Party — Act II of the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_01])
  - Sophomore Party — Act II of the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_15])
  - Sophomore Party — Act III of the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_06])
  - Sophomore Party — Act IV of the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_19])
  - Sophomore Party — Archaeologist and daughter in Act I of the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_11])
  - Sophomore Party — Archaeologist and daughter in the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_12])
  - Sophomore Party — Full cast of the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 63/64 [204_26])
  - Sophomore Party — Full cast of the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_18])
  - Sophomore Party — Prologue scene featuring lotus blossoms in the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_05])
  - Sophomore Party — Prologue scene in the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_17])
  - Sophomore Party — Prologue scene, showing Egyptian women being whipped by their husbands, in the skit show presented by the Class of 1926 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Oct 27 (Box 64 [205_16])
  - Junior Party — "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72 [219_10])
  - Junior Party — "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72 [219_11])
  - Junior Party — "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72 [219_19])
  - Junior Party — "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72 [219_21])
  - Junior Party — "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72/73 [220_09])
  - Junior Party — "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 87 [Box244_005])
  - Junior Party — "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927. The scene includes one student in blackface and wearing what looks like a West Point cadet jacket, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72 [219_09])
  - Junior Party — Antoinette Cooke (VC 1925) portraying Ophelia in "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72/73 [220_11])
  - Junior Party — Mary Steichen (VC 1925) and Emily Zimmerer (VC 1925) portraying Romeo and Juliet in "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72/73 [220_18])
  - Junior Party — Opening scene of "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72/73 [220_12])
  - Junior Party — Opening scene of "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72/73 [220_19])
  - Junior Party — Scene satirizing the Vassar sophomore party tradition in "Be Yourself," a skit show presented by the Class of 1925 to the Class of 1927, 1923 Nov 10 (Box 72/73 [220_15])
  - Latin class play — "The Menaechmi" of Plautus, 1923 Nov 23 (Box 87/88 [Box245_010])
  - Latin class play — "The Menaechmi" of Plautus, 1923 Nov 23 (Box 87/88 [Box245_011])
  - Latin class play — "The Menaechmi" of Plautus, 1923 Nov 23 (Box 88/89 [Box246_021])
  - Latin class play — "The Menaechmi" of Plautus, 1923 Nov 23 (Box 88/89 [Box246_022])
  - Latin class play — "The Menaechmi" of Plautus, 1923 Nov 23 (Box 88/89 [Box246_023])
  - Latin class play — "The Menaechmi" of Plautus, 1923 Nov 23 (Box 89 [Box247_005])
  - Latin class play — "The Menaechmi" of Plautus, 1923 Nov 23 (Box 89 [Box247_011])
  - Latin class play — "The Menaechmi" of Plautus, 1923 Nov 23 (Box 89 [Box247_012])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_001])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_002])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_003])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_004])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_005])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_006])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_007])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_008])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_009])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_010])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_011])
  - First Hall Play — "The School of Princesses,", 1923 Dec 7 (Box 55 [Package73_012])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_001])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_002])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_003])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_004])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_005])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_005cracked])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_006])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_007])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package70_008])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package71_001])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package71_002])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package71_003])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package71_004])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package71_005])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package71_006])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package72_001])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package72_002])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package72_003])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package72_004])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package72_005])
  - First Hall Play — "Beau Brummel,", 1923 Dec 7-8 (Box 54 [Package72_006])
  - Unidentified play — Scene from an unidentified production, 1924 (Box 87/88 [Box245_006])
  - Unidentified play — Scene from an unidentified production, 1924 (Box 87/88 [Box245_007])
  - Unidentified play — Scene from an unidentified production, 1924 (Box 87/88 [Box245_008])
  - Unidentified play — Scene from an unidentified production, 1924 (Box 87/88 [Box245_022])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_02])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_03])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_04])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_05])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_06])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_07])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_08])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_13])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_14])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_15])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_16])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_17])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_18])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_19])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_23])
  - Second Hall Play — "Lady Inger of Ostrat,", 1924 Mar 21-22 (Box 68 [212_24])
  - French Club play — "Le Baiser,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 49 [Package52_001])
  - French Club play — "Le Baiser,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 49 [Package52_003])
  - French Club play — "Le Baiser,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 54 [Package69_001])
  - French Club play — "Le Baiser,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 54 [Package69_005])
  - French Club play — "Le Baiser,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 54 [Package69_006])
  - French Club play — "Le Luthier de Cremone,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 54 [Package69_002])
  - French Club play — "Le Luthier de Cremone,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 54 [Package69_003])
  - French Club play — "Le Luthier de Cremone,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 54 [Package69_004])
  - French Club play — "Le Luthier de Cremone,", 1924 Apr 26 (Box 54 [Package69_007])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1926, 1924 May 5 (Box 73/74 [222_09])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1926, 1924 May 5 (Box 73/74 [222_10])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1926, 1924 May 5 (Box 73/74 [222_11])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1926, 1924 May 5 (Box 73/74 [222_12])
  - Tree Ceremonies — Performance by the Class of 1926, 1924 May 5 (Box 73/74 [222_15])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Kenilworth Revels,", 1924 May 16 (Box 50 [Package54_001])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Kenilworth Revels,", 1924 May 16 (Box 50 [Package54_002])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Kenilworth Revels,", 1924 May 16 (Box 50 [Package54_005])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Kenilworth Revels,", 1924 May 16 (Box 50 [Package55_001])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Kenilworth Revels,", 1924 May 16 (Box 50 [Package55_002])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Kenilworth Revels,", 1924 May 16 (Box 50 [Package55_003])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Kenilworth Revels,", 1924 May 16 (Box 50 [Package55_004])
  - Third Hall Play — "The Kenilworth Revels,", 1924 May 16 (Box 50 [Package55_005])